http://nonprofitfinancefund.org/page/privacy

Skip to main content
Privacy / Terms of UseNFF respects and protects the privacy of our website visitors.Read our full Privacy and Terms of Use statements below.PRIVACY POLICYLast modified: March 23, 2017Introduction Nonprofit Finance Fund® (“NFF” or “we”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website https://nff.org and all subdomains thereof (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.This policy applies to information we collect:On this Website.In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.Through our third party service providers, such as our payment processors, which such information is shared with us.It does not apply to information collected by:us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by NFF or any third party; orany third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website, such as the information collected from our third party service providers not otherwise shared with us.Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your sole choice is to not use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy).Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. Children Under the Age of 13Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information, personal or otherwise, to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at Nonprofit Finance Fund®, 5 Hanover Square 9th Floor, New York, NY 10004 or nff@nff.org.Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, employer, affiliations with entities, any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline or other information you provide to us through the NFF Loan Inquiry feature of the Website (“personal information”);that is about you but individually does not identify you, such as the dates and times of your site visits, the location of your IP address, and other information provided through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies; and/orabout your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.We collect this information:Directly from you when you provide it to us, including through the NFF Loan Inquiry feature of the Website.Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.From third parties, for example, our business partners, payment processers or other third party websites which collect information about you on our behalf.Information You Provide to Us The information we collect on or through our Website may include:Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our services, such as newsletters, commenting on blog posts, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you contact us or report a problem with our Website.Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.Your responses to surveys that you may choose to complete.Your search queries on the Website.Information you provide when applying for an employment opportunity at NFF on the Website.You also may provide information to be published or displayed on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (each, a “Post”). Your Posts are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages or provide you with additional privacy options, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your Posts. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your Posts will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection TechnologiesAs you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information that we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.Speed up your searches.Recognize you when you return to our Website.The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.Web Beacons. Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit NFF, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking TechnologiesSome content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.
We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.Opting Out of Collection of Your Information for Tracking Please refer to your mobile device or browser’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. Depending on your type of device, it may not be possible to delete or disable tracking mechanisms on your mobile device. Note that disabling cookies and/or other tracking tools prevents NFF or its analytics providers from tracking your browser’s activities in relation to your use of the Website. However, doing so may disable many of the features available through the Website. If you have any questions about opting out of the collection of cookies and other tracking/recording tools, you can contact us directly at Nonprofit Finance Fund®, 5 Hanover Square 9th Floor, New York, NY 10004 or nff@nff.org. Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our users, we are not able to respond to Do Not Track signals from your browser or device at this time.How We Use Your InformationWe use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:To present our Website and its contents to you.To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from our Terms of Use.To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.To comply with any applicable governmental requirements.To share the stories of NFF’s clients.In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.For any other purpose with your consent.Disclosure of Your Information We may disclose de-identified and aggregated information about our users without restriction.We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:To our subsidiaries and affiliates.To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.To a successor in interest in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of NFF’s assets, in which personal information held by NFF about our Website users is among the assets transferred.To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.With your consent.We may also disclose your personal information:To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of NFF, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection.We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.Accessing and Correcting Your Information You may also send us an email at nff@nff.org to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.
If you delete your Posts from the Website, copies of your Posts may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including Posts, is governed by our Terms of Use.Your California Privacy Rights California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to nff@nff.org or write us at: Nonprofit Finance Fund®, 5 Hanover Square 9th Floor, New York, NY 10004.Data Security We have implemented reasonable measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like Posts. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.Changes to Our Privacy Policy It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address provided to us or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.Contact Information To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:Nonprofit Finance Fund®, 5 Hanover Square 9th Floor, New York, NY 10004 nff@nff.org DownloadNFF.ORG WEBSITE TERMS OF USELast Modified: March 23, 2017Acceptance of the Terms of Use These terms of use are entered into by and between You and Nonprofit Finance Fund® (“NFF”, “we” or “us”). The following terms and conditions, together with any documents they expressly incorporate by reference (collectively, these “Terms of Use”), govern your access to and use of https://nff.org, and any subdomains thereof as well as any content, functionality and services offered on or through https://nff.org and such subdomains (collectively, the “Website”).Please read the Terms of Use carefully before you start to use the Website. These Terms of Use contain disclaimers, waivers, an indemnification clause, and limitations on our liability. These Terms of Use also contain a class action/jury trial waiver provision that requires the use of court proceedings on an individual basis to resolve disputes, rather than jury trials or class actions. By using the Website, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by these Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy, incorporated herein by reference. If you do not want to agree to these Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the Website.
This Website is offered and available to users who are 18 years of age or older and reside in the United States. By using this Website, you represent and warrant that you are of legal age to form a binding contract with NFF and meet all of the foregoing eligibility requirements. If you do not meet all of these requirements, you must not access or use the Website.Changes to the Terms of Use We may revise and update these Terms of Use from time to time in our sole discretion. All changes are effective immediately when we post them and apply to all access to and use of the Website thereafter. However, any changes to the dispute resolution provisions set forth in Governing Law and Jurisdiction will not apply to any disputes for which the parties have actual notice on or prior to the date the change is posted on the Website.Your continued use of the Website following the posting of revised Terms of Use means that you accept and agree to the changes. You are expected to check this page from time to time so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you.Accessing the Website and Account Security We reserve the right to withdraw or amend this Website, and any service or content we provide on the Website, in our sole discretion without notice. We will not be liable if for any reason all or any part of the Website is unavailable at any time or for any period. From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of the Website, or the entire Website, to users.You are responsible for:Making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to the Website.Ensuring that all persons who access the Website through your Internet connection are aware of these Terms of Use and comply with them.To access the Website or some of the resources it offers, you may be asked to provide certain registration details or other information. It is a condition of your use of the Website that all the information you provide on the Website is correct, current and complete. You agree that all information you provide to register with this Website or otherwise, including but not limited to through the use of any interactive features on the Website, is governed by our Privacy Policy, and you consent to all actions we take with respect to your information consistent with our Privacy Policy.If you choose, or are provided with, a user name, password or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any other person or entity. You also acknowledge that your account is personal to you and agree not to provide any other person with access to this Website or portions of it using your user name, password or other security information. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized access to or use of your user name or password or any other breach of security. You also agree to ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. You should use particular caution when accessing your account from a public or shared computer so that others are not able to view or record your password or other personal information.We have the right to disable any user name, password or other identifier, whether chosen by you or provided by us, at any time in our sole discretion for any or no reason, including if, in our opinion, you have violated any provision of these Terms of Use.Intellectual Property Rights The Website and its entire contents, features and functionality (including but not limited to all information, software, text, displays, images, reports, articles, educational materials, pamphlets, brochures, PDF documents, research, advice, opinions, video and audio, and the design, selection and arrangement thereof), are owned by NFF, its licensors or other providers of such material and are protected by United States and international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret and other intellectual property or proprietary rights laws.These Terms of Use permit you to use the Website for non-commercial use only. You must not reproduce, distribute, modify, create derivative works of, publicly display, publicly perform, republish, download, store or transmit any of the material on our Website, except as follows:Your computer may temporarily store copies of such materials in RAM incidental to your accessing and viewing those materials.You may store files that are automatically cached by your Web browser for display enhancement purposes.You may print or download one copy of a reasonable number of pages of the Website for your own personal, non-commercial use and not for further reproduction, publication or distribution.If we provide interactive features, such as forms or surveys, you may take such actions as are enabled by such features.You must not otherwise:Modify, use, distribute or publish copies of any materials from this site.Delete or alter any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices from copies of materials from this site.You must not access or use for any commercial purposes any part of the Website or any services or materials available through the Website.If you wish to make any use of material on the Website other than that set out in this section, please address your request to: nff@nfff.org.If you print, copy, modify, download or otherwise use or provide any other person with access to any part of the Website in breach of the Terms of Use, your right to use the Website will cease immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made. No right, title or interest in or to the Website or any content on the Website is transferred to you, and all rights not expressly granted are reserved by NFF. Any use of the Website not expressly permitted by these Terms of Use is a breach of these Terms of Use and may violate copyright, trademark and other laws.Trademarks The Nonprofit Finance Fund® name, the terms Financial SCAN, NFF, and Where Money Meets Mission, the NFF logo and all related names, logos, product and service names, designs and slogans are trademarks of NFF or its affiliates or licensors. You must not use such marks without the prior written permission of NFF. All other names, logos, product and service names, designs and slogans on this Website are the trademarks of their respective owners.Prohibited Uses You may use the Website only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms of Use. You agree not to use the Website:In any way that violates any applicable federal, state, local or international law or regulation (including, without limitation, any laws regarding the export of data or software to and from the US or other countries).To impersonate or attempt to impersonate NFF, a NFF employee, another user or any other person or entity (including, without limitation, by using e-mail addresses associated with any of the foregoing).To engage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits anyone’s use or enjoyment of the Website, or which, as determined by us, may harm NFF or users of the Website or expose them to liability.Additionally, you agree not to:Use the Website in any manner that could disable, overburden, damage, or impair the site or interfere with any other party’s use of the Website, including their ability to engage in real time activities through the Website.Use any robot, spider or other automatic device, process or means to access the Website for any purpose, including monitoring or copying any of the material on the Website.Use any manual process to monitor or copy any of the material on the Website or for any other unauthorized purpose without our prior written consent.Use any device, software or routine that interferes with the proper working of the Website.Introduce any viruses, trojan horses, worms, logic bombs or other material which is malicious or technologically harmful.Attempt to gain unauthorized access to, interfere with, damage or disrupt any parts of the Website, the server on which the Website is stored, or any server, computer or database connected to the Website.Attack the Website via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of-service attack.Otherwise attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Website.User Contributions The Website contains a blog and other interactive features (collectively, “Interactive Services”) that allow users to comment, submit, or display their responses, opinions or other original thought content (each, a “Post”) on or through the Website.All Posts must comply with the Content Standards set out in these Terms of Use.
Any Post to the Website will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary. By providing any Post on the Website, you grant us and our affiliates and service providers, and each of their and our respective licensees, successors and assigns the right to use, reproduce, modify, perform, display, distribute and otherwise disclose to third parties any such material for any purpose.You represent and warrant that:You own or control all rights in and to the content of your Posts and have the right to grant the license granted above to us and our affiliates and service providers, and each of their and our respective licensees, successors and assigns.All of your Posts do and will comply with these Terms of Use.You understand and acknowledge that you are responsible for any Post you submit or contribute, and you, not NFF, have full responsibility for such content, including its legality, reliability, accuracy and appropriateness.We are not responsible, or liable to any third party, for the content or accuracy of any Post made by you or any other user of the Website.Monitoring and Enforcement; Termination We have the right to:Remove or refuse to display any Post for any or no reason in our sole discretion.Take any action with respect to any Post that we deem necessary or appropriate in our sole discretion, including if we believe that such Post violate the Terms of Use, including the Content Standards, infringes any intellectual property right or other right of any person or entity, threatens the personal safety of users of the Website or the public or could create liability for NFF.Disclose your identity or other information about you to any third party who claims that material posted by you violates their rights, including their intellectual property rights or their right to privacy.Take appropriate legal action, including without limitation, referral to law enforcement, for any illegal or unauthorized use of the Website.Terminate or suspend your access to all or part of the Website for any or no reason, including without limitation, any violation of these Terms of Use.Without limiting the foregoing, we have the right to fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity or other information of anyone posting any materials on or through the Website. YOU WAIVE AND HOLD HARMLESS NFF AND ITS AFFILIATES, LICENSEES AND SERVICE PROVIDERS FROM ANY CLAIMS RESULTING FROM ANY ACTION TAKEN BY NFF DURING OR AS A RESULT OF ITS INVESTIGATIONS AND FROM ANY ACTIONS TAKEN AS A CONSEQUENCE OF INVESTIGATIONS BY EITHER NFF OR LAW ENFORCEMENT AUTHORITIES.However, we do not undertake to review Posts before they are posted on the Website, and cannot ensure prompt removal of objectionable material after it has been posted. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any action or inaction regarding transmissions, communications or content provided by any user or third party. We have no liability or responsibility to anyone for performance or nonperformance of the activities described in this section.Content Standards These content standards apply to any and all Posts and use of Interactive Services. Posts must in their entirety comply with all applicable federal, state, local and international laws and regulations. Without limiting the foregoing, Posts must not:Contain any material which is defamatory, obscene, indecent, abusive, offensive, harassing, violent, hateful, inflammatory or otherwise objectionable. Promote violence, or discrimination based on race, sex, religion, nationality, disability, sexual orientation or age.Infringe any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other intellectual property or other rights of any other person.Violate the legal rights (including the rights of publicity and privacy) of others or contain any material that could give rise to any civil or criminal liability under applicable laws or regulations or that otherwise may be in conflict with these Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy.Be likely to deceive any person.Promote any illegal activity, or advocate, promote or assist any unlawful act.Cause annoyance, inconvenience or needless anxiety or be likely to upset, embarrass, alarm or annoy any other person.Impersonate any person, or misrepresent your identity or affiliation with any person or organization.Involve commercial activities or sales, such as contests, sweepstakes and other sales promotions, barter or advertising.Give the impression that they emanate from or are endorsed by us or any other person or entity, if this is not the case.Reliance on Information Posted The information presented on or through the Website is made available solely for general information purposes. We do not warrant the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of this information. Any reliance you place on such information is strictly at your own risk. We disclaim all liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such materials by you or any other visitor to the Website, or by anyone who may be informed of any of its contents.This Website includes content provided by third parties, including materials provided by other users, bloggers and third-party licensors, syndicators, aggregators and/or reporting services . All statements and/or opinions expressed in these materials, and all articles and responses to questions and other content, other than the content provided by NFF, are solely the opinions and the responsibility of the person or entity providing those materials. These materials do not necessarily reflect the opinion of NFF. We are not responsible, or liable to you or any third party, for the content or accuracy of any materials provided by any third parties.Changes to the Website We may update the content on this Website from time to time, but its content is not necessarily complete or up-to-date. Any of the material on the Website may be out of date at any given time, and we are under no obligation to update such material.Information About You and Your Visits to the Website All information we collect on this Website is subject to our Privacy Policy. By using the Website, you consent to all actions taken by us with respect to your information in compliance with the Privacy Policy.Online Purchases and Other Terms and Conditions All purchases through our site, other transactions for the sale of goods, webinars, services or information formed through the Website or as a result of visits made by you, or donations to us made through our PayPal account, are governed by the terms of use of each applicable third-party service provider processing your payment for the foregoing, which are hereby incorporated into these Terms of Use.
Additional terms and conditions may also apply to specific portions, services or features of the Website. All such additional terms and conditions are hereby incorporated by this reference into these Terms of Use.Linking to the Website You may link to our homepage, provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal and does not damage our reputation or take advantage of it, but you must not establish a link in such a way as to suggest any form of association, approval or endorsement on our part without our express written consent.Links from the Website If the Website contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your convenience only. This includes links contained in advertisements, including banner advertisements, sponsored links, links to our third party business partners or third party payment processors. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. If you decide to access any of the third-party websites linked to this Website, you do so entirely at your own risk and subject to the terms and conditions of use for such websites.Geographic Restrictions The owner of the Website is based in the State of New York in the United States. We provide this Website for use only by persons located in the United States. We make no claims that the Website or any of its content is accessible or appropriate outside of the United States. Access to the Website may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Website from outside the United States, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.Disclaimer of Warranties You understand that we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant that files available for downloading from the Internet or the Website will be free of viruses or other destructive code. You are responsible for implementing sufficient procedures and checkpoints to satisfy your particular requirements for anti-virus protection and accuracy of data input and output, and for maintaining a means external to our site for any reconstruction of any lost data. WE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY A DISTRIBUTED DENIAL-OF-SERVICE ATTACK, VIRUSES OR OTHER TECHNOLOGICALLY HARMFUL MATERIAL THAT MAY INFECT YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT, COMPUTER PROGRAMS, DATA OR OTHER PROPRIETARY MATERIAL DUE TO YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR TO YOUR DOWNLOADING OF ANY MATERIAL POSTED ON IT, OR ON ANY WEBSITE LINKED TO IT. YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT AND ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT AND ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. NEITHER NFF NOR ANY PERSON ASSOCIATED WITH NFF MAKES ANY WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION WITH RESPECT TO THE COMPLETENESS, SECURITY, RELIABILITY, QUALITY, ACCURACY OR AVAILABILITY OF THE WEBSITE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, NEITHER NFF NOR ANYONE ASSOCIATED WITH NFF REPRESENTS OR WARRANTS THAT THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE WILL BE ACCURATE, RELIABLE, ERROR-FREE OR UNINTERRUPTED, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, THAT OUR SITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS OR THAT THE WEBSITE OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE WILL OTHERWISE MEET YOUR NEEDS OR EXPECTATIONS.NFF HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT AND FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE.THE FOREGOING DOES NOT AFFECT ANY WARRANTIES WHICH CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.Limitation on Liability IN NO EVENT WILL NFF, ITS AFFILIATES OR THEIR LICENSORS, SERVICE PROVIDERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, OFFICERS OR DIRECTORS BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE, OR INABILITY TO USE, THE WEBSITE, ANY WEBSITES LINKED TO IT, ANY CONTENT ON THE WEBSITE OR SUCH OTHER WEBSITES OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR SUCH OTHER WEBSITES, INCLUDING ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PERSONAL INJURY, PAIN AND SUFFERING, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, LOSS OF REVENUE, LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR ANTICIPATED SAVINGS, LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF GOODWILL, LOSS OF DATA, AND WHETHER CAUSED BY TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), BREACH OF CONTRACT OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF FORESEEABLE.THE FOREGOING DOES NOT AFFECT ANY LIABILITY WHICH CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.Indemnification You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless NFF, its affiliates, licensors and service providers, and its and their respective officers, directors, employees, contractors, agents, licensors, suppliers, successors and assigns from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, judgments, awards, losses, costs, expenses or fees (including reasonable attorneys’ fees) arising out of or relating to your violation of these Terms of Use or your use of the Website, including, but not limited to, your Posts, use of the Website’s content, services and products other than as expressly authorized in these Terms of Use or your use of any information obtained from the Website.Governing Law and Jurisdiction All matters relating to the Website and these Terms of Use and any dispute or claim arising therefrom or related thereto (in each case, including non-contractual disputes or claims), shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of New York without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law provision or rule (whether of the State of New York or any other jurisdiction). Any legal suit, action or proceeding arising out of, or related to, these Terms of Use or the Website shall be instituted exclusively in the federal courts of the United States or the courts of the State of New York in each case located in the City of New York and County of New York although we retain the right to bring any suit, action or proceeding against you for breach of these Terms of Use in your country of residence or any other relevant country. You waive any and all objections to the exercise of jurisdiction over you by such courts and to venue in such courts. WITH RESPECT TO ALL PERSONS, ALL CLAIMS MUST BE BROUGHT IN A PARTY’S INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY, AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY PURPORTED CLASS ACTION, COLLECTIVE ACTION, PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL ACTION OR OTHER REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING. THIS WAIVER APPLIES TO CLASS ARBITRATION, AND, UNLESS NFF AGREES OTHERWISE, THE COURT OF COMPETENT JURISDICTION MAY NOT CONSOLIDATE MORE THAN ONE PERSON’S CLAIMS. YOU AGREE THAT, BY AGREEING TO THESE RULES, YOU AND NFF ARE EACH WAIVING THE RIGHT TO A TRIAL BY JURY OR TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION, COLLECTIVE ACTION, PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL ACTION, OR OTHER REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING OF ANY KIND.Limitation on Time to File Claims ANY CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS OF USE OR THE WEBSITE MUST BE COMMENCED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES, OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM IS PERMANENTLY BARRED.Waiver and Severability No waiver by NFF of any term or condition set forth in these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or a waiver of any other term or condition, and any failure of NFF to assert a right or provision under these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of these Terms of Use is held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable for any reason, such provision shall be eliminated or limited to the minimum extent such that the remaining provisions of the Terms of Use will continue in full force and effect.Entire Agreement The Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy constitute the sole and entire agreement between you and Nonprofit Finance Fund® with respect to the Website and supersede all prior and contemporaneous understandings, agreements, representations and warranties, both written and oral, with respect to the Website.Your Comments and Concerns This website is operated by Nonprofit Finance Fund®, 5 Hanover Square 9th Floor, New York, NY 10004.All other feedback, comments, requests for technical support and other communications relating to the Website should be directed to: nff@nff.org. Download Clear All FiltersArts and CultureEducationHealthHousingHuman ServicesNonprofit SectorFinancial ManagementFull CostsImpact InvestingCapitalizationOutcomesFinancingConsultingPartnerLearnHomeCOVID-19About usEquity at NFFCareersContactSearch NFF
